fabguys.com 2019-06-19

# privacy_policy

##  PRIVACY AND COOKIES POLICY 

Effective Date: 25th May 2018 

## The Basics

We're absolutely committed to protecting the privacy and security of all Users. We use this site too. The data controller is Winchester Consultancy Ltd and you can contact us using this form with any data/privacy queries. 

1\. **SIMPLE** : We only use your data for core functions like creating your profile, using the site, and improving your experience. 

2\. **SECURE** : We use the site ourselves and have our own data on here and we've been keeping it safe and secure for over 10 years. 

3\. **NO SPAM** : We don't send any marketing messages. Email notifications for stuff like message notifications are all opt-in only (you can control from email notifications page). 

4\. **WHEN YOU'RE GONE, YOU'RE GONE**. If you delete your account, it's not recoverable from the instant you hit the Delete button. All data is securely and automatically deleted in line with our legal obligations. 

## The Details

**What's the point of this policy?**

It tells you what to expect when we collect your personal information. Please only use our service if you are completely happy with this policy. 

Generally, the policy covers only information provided to us. If you give personal information to other people, such as payment providers or other websites, please check their privacy policies. 

**Might the policy change?**

Yes. We will assume you agree to the new version of the policy if you use the site after its effective date. 

**What do we collect?**

Information which you upload to our service or otherwise give us when registering or completing your profile. This may include “special category data” such as details about your race / racial origin, sex life and/or sexual orientation. 

Automated information such as the internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your device to the internet, connection information such as browser type and version, information about your device including device-type, operating system and platform, a unique reference number linked to the data you enter on our system, login details, clickstream data, details of your activity with date / time stamps including pages you visited and your searches / transactions. 

If you Upgrade by text from an 18+ registered phone, upgrade by credit card that is only available to adults 18+ we may store an 18+ verified flag as part of your account data (to clarify, we do not store or are passed any other details about the upgrade). This will not be visible as part of your public profile. We may also store an 18+ verified flag if you perform other actions on the site that conform to relevant regulations and prove you are an adult 18+. We may make use of this 18+ data at our discretion or if required by law in a particular country. 

**What's our legal basis for collecting the information?**

Because it's necessary to provide you with our services under our contract with you. We also collect the “special category data” (see above) in accordance with your explicit consent, for example during the setup of your profile page. In the case of automated information collected when you browse your site, we use this to manage and improve our service in accordance with our “legitimate interests”. 

**What about cookies?**

We and/or third parties use cookies and other tracking technologies on our website. A cookie is an identifier (a small file of letters and numbers) that is sent to your computer. Our website's functionality will be limited if you configure your browser to reject cookies. 

Cookies are widely used to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the website owner or others. Session cookies are temporary cookies that remain in the cookie file of your browser only until your browser is closed. They allow websites to link your actions during a browser session. Persistent cookies stay in the cookie file of your browser for longer (how long will depend on the lifetime of the specific cookie). For further information on cookies, including how to use your browser to block them and how to delete cookies already stored on your device, visit: www.allaboutcookies.org. 

The following kinds of cookies may be used on this website: 

Session cookies: They allow you to proceed through many pages of the site quickly and easily without having to authenticate or reprocess each new area you visit. 

Log-in (“remember me”) cookies: Persistent cookies remember your details and speed up your log-in when you return to our website. 

Google cookies: Persistent cookies are set in connection with the following Google services on our site: 

Google Analytics (“GA”): We use cookies to recognise and count the number of website visitors as well as providing other information about the visit such as duration, route through the website and what sites the visitor came from. This information helps us to improve the way our website works. 

By continuing to use our website we assume that you consent to use of the cookies outlined above. 

**What do we do with personal information?**

Provide our service, e.g. allow you to create an online profile, send service messages, process payments, fulfil orders. 

Use it for age or other verification purposes. 

Use your “special category data” (e.g. details about your race / racial origin, sex life and/or sexual orientation) to enable you to display this information to other users. 

Send you notification messages (for example, when you have a new private message), if you have opted in. You can change your email preferences on the email notifications page. 

Use it to recognise you when you visit or return to our service to track anonymised traffic and usage patterns, prevent or detect fraud or abuses and help us improve our service. 

**How long do we keep it?**

We will delete your personal information when you choose to delete your account, using the remove account page. Your account is permanently deleted and will not be recoverable from the moment you delete it. All data is fully removed in line with legal timescale guidelines / requirements for deletion of such data. We may also delete your account after period of inactivity or at our discretion (for example, if our Terms and Conditions are breached). 

**To whom do we send or make available your personal information?**

To other users of our service, if you enter personal information into your public profile or otherwise include it in a post, comment or other public action on our service. Please note: 

Viewing another user’s profile will be notified to the profile-owner unless you have opted out on your privacy page. 

Public actions by you for example, entering a chat room, making a forum post, updating your status, uploading a public photo or participating in a chat may be listed in newsfeeds of other users. If you hide your profile from your privacy page, your activities won’t be shown in newsfeeds but may still be visible in the place where you took the action. 

Certain of your activities are displayed on your profile page including date joined and date last logged in. This information can be removed only by hiding your profile. 

NB Your “special category data” (e.g. details you have entered on your profile about your race / racial origin, sex life and/or sexual orientation) will be included in the profile information displayed to other users. 

To the police or other relevant authorities or if disclosure is necessary to protect us or others, or if a criminal act may have been committed, or where required by law or where requested by the police or other appropriate authorities. 

To buyers so far as reasonably necessary in the case of sale or merger or business combination involving all or the relevant part of our business. 

You can find options to control privacy aspects of the site on your privacy page. 

**What happens to your payment details?**

These go direct to our payment partners. We do not receive such information. To ensure your details are not being used without consent, our payment partners may send your personal information to relevant third parties including credit reference and fraud prevention agencies. 

**Do we send your information outside the European Union?**

Your personal information which we collect is stored within the EU and is not transferred to any third countries. 

**What rights do you have?**

If the legal requirements are met: To ask us for access to your personal information, to rectify it if there are mistakes, to delete or restrict or object to its use in certain circumstances or to “data portability”. 

If you have a complaint about how we are dealing with your personal information, please contact us via the contact form. If you are not happy with our response or think we are not handling your personal information in accordance with the law, you can complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO). 

For more information about your rights, visit the ICO’s website: www.ico.org.uk. 

**Changing your settings**

You can change your pribacy settings at any time with the privacy page if you are logged in. You can change your email notifications here. 

You can remove yourself and all your data from the site at any time using the remove page.
